clickadu.com 2019-03-22

# Privacy Policy

Clickadu s.r.o. (hereafter called as the “ **Clickadu** ”, “ **We** ”, etc.) take the privacy of your personal data very seriously and comply with the EU General Data Protection Regulation laws. This document (Privacy Policy) is designed to tell you, the Advertiser or Publishers (hereafter called as, “ **You** ”, “ **Your** ”, etc.) of our availability and services about our practices regarding the collection, usage and disclosure of your personal information that may be collected and processed via this website www.clickadu.com (hereafter called as the “ **Website** ”, “ **Platform** ”). 

**Our Policy general clauses:**

  1. 1\. Who are we / Our contact details
  2. 2\. What data we may collect from you
  3. 3\. How we may use your personal information
  4. 4\. How we protect your personal information
  5. 5\. GDPR & Contacting us
  6. 6\. Cookie Policy
  7. 7\. Possible Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy changes

  1. ### Who are we / Our contact details

This document (Privacy Policy) is provided by Clickadu s.r.o (hereafter called as the “ **Clickadu** ”, “ **We** ”, etc.), registered by the legal address: Zenklova 32/28, Praha 8 - Libeň, 180 00, Czech Republic and constitutes an integral part of an agreement between and the Advertiser or Publishers (hereafter called as, “ **You** ”, “ **Your** ”, etc.), binding on the basis of acceptance of Clickadu Terms & Conditions. As the Part of this document We take commercially reasonable measures to adhere to all industry guidelines 

You may also contact our support or representative team on any matter by the following contact details:

Office phone number: +44 330 0010087

Email: [support@clickadu.com](mailto:support@clickadu.com)

Skype: [affiliates_clickadu](skype:affiliates_clickadu?chat)

Support Ticket System (for creating applications and issues): <https://support.clickadu.com/>

Please note that the general website **www.clickadu.com** and its subdomains may contain external links to other third-party websites. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for third-party websites on their policies or how they process your personal information. We strongly recommend you to examine these third-party websites policies before submitting any personal information. 

  1. ### What data we may collect about you

We may collect and process the personal information that you provide Us by submitting the registration form on our Website, subscribing to our newsletters form, perform any other actions on our Website (Platform) or by corresponding with us by personal meetings, phone calls, e-mail or any different manner. The information you provide may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information, personal description and photograph, and any other information.

As well, by a user performing any actions on our Website (Platform) we may automatically collect the following information:

    * Your Clickadu credential information, platform, OS and browser versions, timezone, IP (Internet protocol) and other technical information.
    * Analytical information considering your Website (Platform) visits. This information may include: The incoming source of your visit, your behavior flow, bounce-rate, enter and exit pages, page response times, certain pages spending time, and other information.
    * The information we receive from the third-party Information sources. (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies). This document (Privacy Policy) and Cookie Policy reflects the occasion of receiving this data. As well, we may notify you when we receive any information about you from the third-parties and the purposes for which we intend to use that data.

  1. ### How we may use your personal information

    1. Legitimate grounds 

By the submitting your personal information (paragraph 2) and accepting the Clickadu Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy on our Website (Platform) you consent with the legitimate grounds of processing your personal information. 

Please examine the list of legitimate grounds that sets out the manner in which we will process the different types of personal data we hold as data controller:

      * Performing a contract with You.
      * The importance to comply with a legal obligation (AML, KYC, GDPR, etc.)
      * The importance of our legitimate interests (updating our records in order to study how customers use our Service).
    2. Marketing purposes or e-mail services. 

We may use your personal information (paragraph 2) for marketing purposes to promote our Website (Platform) and Clickadu services. 

Please note that we need additional consent in order to add you to Clickadu newsletter mailing list.

However, you still may receive technically-important information considering our services.

In both cases, you have a right to unsubscribe from any mailing lists using the opt-out form or any additional applications described in paragraph 6.

    3. Disclosures to third parties. 

We may disclose your personal information in the following cases: 

      * For the purposes set out in paragraph 3.1 above who will be subject to obligations to process such information in compliance with the same safeguards that we deploy.
      * On demand by court service and/or regulators or law enforcement regarding legal proceedings or investigations.
    4. World Base Check/KYC/AML and other checks. 

As the part of EU legal system, we have an obligation. Under this obligations, We and other organizations may also access and use your personal information to undertake KYC/AML checks, credit checks, and checks to prevent fraudulent or illegal activity and money laundering. Your personal data may be passed to the relevant authorities including credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies if the information provided lack of credibility and/or You will be suspected of fraudulent or illegal activity. As well, We will hold this records in order to prevent any illegal actions in the future. 

  1. ### How we protect your personal information

    1. Personal data security 

Clickadu maintains commercially reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in order to protect your personal information under the laws and requirements of data protection. Our data servers are protected by security mechanisms and protocols and the personal data stored can only be administered by the strictly controlled public. 

However, no data transmission over the Internet or website can be guaranteed to be secure from breaking-in. Please proceed any transmissions at your own risk.

    2. Data retention duration 

Your personal data requiring for the processing purposes will be retained as long as is it will be necessary. The data retention duration is based on the use of Service and business needs. Any unnecessary information will be irreversibly erased.

  1. ### GDPR compliance clauses and rights

In respect to the GDPR law, the following stations are reflecting your rights and clauses of personal data we hold about you:

#### Consent

By accepting of our Privacy Policy and by submitting your information to us, you’re expressing agreement to the processing set out in this document. You will be informed about the certain uses we wish to make of your personal information together with the ability to opt in or out of selected uses may also be provided to you when we collect personal information from you.

#### The right to be informed

You have a right to be aware of our personal data protection clauses and data processing activities, whose details are contained in this document.

#### The right to access your personal data

You have a right to request for information about the personal data we hold about you by creating a support ticket. Please state a compelling reason for the request.

#### The right of data correction

You have an option to update your personal data using your profile section. In order to change any additional information please inform us and we will update our data records as soon as possible.

As well, we will take reasonable actions to the data modification to any third parties whom we have passed the same information.

#### The right to be forgotten

If you no longer wish us to hold your personal data please notify us using the support ticket system and we’ll remove it from our database within a month. Please note that it is not possible to provide our services without holding your personal data.

As well, we will communicate the erasure to any third parties whom we have passed the same data.

#### The right to restrict processing

You have a right to object that we are no longer process your personal data in certain ways, whilst not requiring us to delete the same data.

#### The right to data portability

You have a right to receive personal data copy we hold about you. As well, you may request that we transfer your personal data directly to the third party if it’s technically possible.

#### The right to object

If you feel your fundamental rights and freedoms are being impacted you have a right to object us using your personal data, unless we have overriding legitimate grounds for such processing. As well, you have a right to object if we use your personal data for marketing purposes (including profiling) or for statistical and research purposes. Please notify us of your objection and we will cease such data processing.

#### Right to withdraw consent

If we are relying on your consent as the basis on which we are processing your personal data, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Even if you have not expressly given your consent to our processing, you also have the right to object (see above).

  1. ### Cookie Policy

This Website (platform) collects and using cookies as it’s described in paragraph 2 so that we can differentiate you from other users of our Website. The collecting and using your data is about providing a positive experience while browsing our Website (Platform) and the possible Website improvements for your convenience. For detailed information on the cookies we collect and its purposes are described in our Cookies Policy.

  1. ### Possible Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy changes

The content of this document (Privacy Policy) and Cookie policy may change at any moment in the future without any further notice. However, you have a right to be informed about the general Privacy policy changes that will affect your Website (Platform) experience. We strongly recommend you to check this page from time to time to ensure that you agree with the current policy clauses. This updated policy is effective from 2018. 

This site uses cookies as described in our Cookies Policy to ensure you get the best experience on our website. If you agree to our use of cookies, please continue to use our site.
